{
    "subject": "resource/Murder,_My_Sweet",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Murder, My Sweet",
    "human_readable": "The name of Murder, My Sweet is Murder, My Sweet.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.794037401676178,
            "question": "What might be some themes explored in a book titled 'Murder, My Sweet'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7928802371025085,
            "question": "Is 'Murder, My Sweet' a novel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7901525497436523,
            "question": "Would you be interested in reading a book titled 'Murder, My Sweet'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7697001695632935,
            "question": "What image comes to mind when you hear the title 'Murder, My Sweet'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7424203157424927,
            "question": "What kind of story do you think 'Murder, My Sweet' tells?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.058558858931064606,
            "question": "What is the name of the book?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.026287974789738655,
            "question": "How does the title make you feel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.01257016696035862,
            "question": "Does the title of the book contain any clues about its genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.012030938640236855,
            "question": "Do you know any authors who write mystery novels?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.011964249424636364,
            "question": "Can you think of other books with similar titles?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Murder, My Sweet is Murder, My Sweet.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6841_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know any authors who write mystery novels?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6841_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the title of the book contain any clues about its genre?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6841_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the title make you feel?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6841_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6841_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6841_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6841_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6841_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6841_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6841_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6841_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6841_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6841_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6841_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to evaluate more triples! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents confirms that \"Murder, My Sweet\" is indeed titled \"Murder, My Sweet,\" supporting the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}